A Guide to the City College of New York collection of the Russell Sage Foundation Library FA1208
Rockefeller Archive Center
- How Tax Exemption Broke the Housing Deadlock in New York City, 1960 (Box 7)
- In the Great Tradition: 11th Convention, UAW-CIO, 1945 (Box 7)
- Shop Paper Handbook, 1946 (Box 7)
- The ILWU Story: Three Decades of Militant Unionism, 1963 (Box 7)
- UAW Fair Practices Fact Sheet (32 Sheets), 1956-1969 (Box 7)
- Clinical Notes on the Disorders of Childhood, 1931 (Box 7)
- The Housing Market in New York City, 1944 (Box 7)
- The Gang: A Study of 1,313 Gangs in Chicago, 1936 (Box 7)
- Labor's Stake in Abolishing the Poll Tax, 1943 (Box 7)
- Memorandum on Post War Urban Housing, 1944 (Box 7)
- Politics in Housing, 1944 (Box 7)
- Fruits of Victory: Poverty or Plenty, 1944 (Box 7)
- Homes for Workers in Planned Communities Thru Collective Action, 1943 (Box 7)
- America Tomorrow, 1943 (Box 7)
- Rent and Income Policies in Public Housing, 1968 (Box 7)
- Recent Trends in Housing in the United States, Paper given by Sydney Maslen, 1942 (Box 7)
- Relocation of Residential Site Tenants in New York City with Special Reference to the Title I of the Housing Act of 1949, 1956 (Box 7)
- Relocation of Residential Site Tenants in New York City with Special Reference to the Title I of the Housing Act of 1949, 1956 (Box 7)
- The St. Mark's Neighborhood, 1941-1943 (Box 7A)
- The St. Mark's Neighborhood, 1941-1943 (Box 7A)
- The Region's Growth: Regional Plan Association, 1967 (Box 7A)
- The Social Questions Bulletin Vols. 16-18, 1926-1938 (Box 7A)
- The Social Questions Bulletin Vols. 19-23, 1926-1938 (Box 7A)
- The Social Questions Bulletin Vols. 24-28, 1926-1938 (Box 7A)
- Agricultural Co-operation In its Application to the Industry, 1925 (Box 7A)
- Survey of the Literature on Brazil of Sociological Significance Published Up to 1940, 1945 (Box 7A)
- A Bibliography of Social Surveys: Reports of Fact-finding Studies Made as a Basis for Social Action; Arranged by Subjects and Localities, 1930 (Box 7A)
- The Vocational Guidance Magazine: Organ of The National Vocational Guidance Association, 1929 (Box 7B)
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation: The First Eleven Years 1930-1941, 1942 (Box 7B)
- Children and Their Parents, 1932 (Box 7B)
- Municipal Reform Movements, 1895 (Box 7B)
- Community Welfare Week by William Lloyd Davis (Box 7B)
- Report for, 1929-1941 (Box 7B)
- Monthly Vital Statistics Review, 1920 (Box 7B)
- Twenty-Sixth Annual Report and Documents of the New York Institution for the institution of the Deaf and Dumb 26-30 (Box 7B)
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation Annual Report, 1963 (Box 7C)
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation Annual Report, 1964 (Box 7C)
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation Annual Report, 1965 (Box 7C)
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation Annual Report, 1975 (Box 7C)
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation Annual Report, 1968 (Box 7C)
- Twenty-first Annual Report of the Trustees of the State Lunatic Hospital at Taunton, 1874 (Box 7C)
- New York (City). City Magistrates, Board of (First Division) Annual Report. 1907-1909, 1898-1913 (Box 7C)
- Church Social Union Publications, 1895-1910 (Box 8)
- National Conference on Outdoor Recreation, 1924-1928 (Box 8)
- Challenge of Childhood: studies in personality and behavior, 1926 (Box 8)
- Report of The Christian Embassy to Japan, 1915 (Box 8)
- Social Service and the Episcopal Church, 1913 (Box 8)
- The Social Task of the Church as Set Forth by the Lambeth Conference of 1920 (Box 8)
- The First Five Years, 1942 (Box 8)
- Automobile Unionism by R.J. Thomas, 1944 (Box 8)
- A Review of the First Decade and a Preview of the Second, 1957 (Box 8)
- Management Controls: An Annotated Bibliography, 1953 (Box 8)
- Perspective for Business Expansion - A Memorandum to Kalamazoo Businessmen, 1949 (Box 8)
- Research Report on Integrated Housing in Kalamazoo, 1959 (Box 8)
- The Position of the Paper Industry in the Economy of Kalamazoo County Michigan in 1954, 1958 (Box 8)
- The UAW-CIO Post War Plan (Box 8)
- To Unite Regardless, 1943 (Box 8)
- Building the Union: A Handbook for Local Union Education Committees, 1945 (Box 8)
- How to Speak at Union Meetings, 1943 (Box 8)
- National Conference on Motion Pictures Report, 1929 (Box 8)
- Kalamazoo in 1975: Talks Given by Harold C. Taylor and Smauel Bennett to The Council of Social Agencies, 1958 (Box 8)
- Resources for Industry in Kalamazoo, 1950 (Box 8)
- CSR Foreground Studies: The Family in the United States, 1958 (Box 8)
- Who's Who of the Twentieth Century Fund, 1941 (Box 8)
- Hours of work, 1952 (Box 8)
- Purchasing Power for Prosperity: The Case of the General Motors Workers For Maintaining Take-home Pay, 1945 (Box 8)
- Book of the Camp Fire Girls, 1948 (Box 8)
- Industrial Education: a necessary part of public education, 1883 (Box 8)
- Studies in Sociology: Legal Training for Social Workers, 1916 (Box 8)
- Social Service for Young People in the Church School by Clara Bancroft Beatley, 1900-1993 (Box 8)
- Disasters and the American Red Cross in Disaster Relief, 1918 (Box 8)
- Youth in Conflict by Miriam Van Waters, 1932 (Box 8)
- Needy Spain: A Report on Relief Word by Dan West, 1938 (Box 8)
- War Relief in Spain: Report to the American Unitarian Association by Alfred W. and Mary Carter Jones, 1938 (Box 8)
- Refugee Facts, 1939 (Box 8)
- What About the Conscientious Objector, 1940 (Box 8A)
- United States of America Vs. Arle Brooks, 1941 (Box 8A)
- Pacifist Living Today and Tomorrow, 1941 (Box 8A)
- Race and Class in Rural Brazil, 1952 (Box 8A)
- Second Triennial Report, 1916 (Box 8A)
- Ethical Frontiers: Broken Homes, 1956 (Box 8A)
- The Social Opportunity of the Churchman, 1924 (Box 8A)
- Social Service Through the Parish, 1923 (Box 8A)
- The Board of Public Education School District Of Philadelphia, 1923 (Box 8A)
- The Board of Public Education School District Of Philadelphia, 1921 (Box 8A)
- The Board of Public Education School District Of Philadelphia, 1922 (Box 8A)
- The Board of Public Education School District Of Philadelphia, 1924 (Box 8A)
- The Board of Public Education School District Of Philadelphia, 1925 (Box 8A)
- The Board of Public Education School District Of Philadelphia, 1926 (Box 8A)
- The Board of Public Education School District Of Philadelphia, 1927 (Box 8A)
- The Board of Public Education School District Of Philadelphia, 1928 (Box 8A)
- The Board of Public Education School District Of Philadelphia, 1929 (Box 8A)
- The Board of Public Education School District Of Philadelphia, 1930 (Box 8A)
- Christianity and Industrial Relations by B. Seebohm Rowntree, 1937 (Box 8A)
- The Family Today, 1958 (Box 8A)
- Strikes and Democratic Government: A Report by the Labor Committee of The Twentieth Century Fund, 1947 (Box 8A)
- Our Church Industrial High Schools for Negroes, 1925 (Box 8A)
- Handbook of Church Publicity, 1922 (Box 8A)
- A comprehensive immigration policy and program, Sidney Gulick, 1915 (Box 8A)
- Report of Special Meeting Cleveland, Ohio, 1919 (Box 8A)
- Federal Council Bulletin, 1918-1950 (Box 8A)
- Report of College Conference on Training Recreation Leaders, 1937 (Box 8A)
- A Survey of Institutional Research on American Postwar Problems, 1942 (Box 8A)
- America's Capital Requirements Estimates for 1946-1960, 1950 (Box 8A)
- U.S.A. Measure of a Nation: A Graphic Presentation of America's Needs and Resources, 1949 (Box 8A)
- Official War Publications Guide to State and Federal Publications, 1941 (Box 8A)
- Official War Publications Guide to State, Federal, and Canadian Publications Second Supplement to Official Defense Publication, 1942-1945 (Box 8A)
- The Housing of the Unskilled Wage Earner (Box 8B)
- Industrial Psychology (Box 8B)
- American Unitarian Association (Bulletin 21-35) (Box 8B)
- The Hours of Workers (Box 8B)
- The Carnegie United Kingdom Trust (Annual Reports), 1939-1956 (Box 8B)
- The Carnegie United Kingdom Trust (Annual Reports), 1957-1966 (Box 8B)
- The Canadian Social Science Research Council (Reports 1-17), 1940-1960 (Box 8B)
- Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation - Annual Reports (9 Reports), 1940-1961 (Box 8B)
- Annual Report of the Division of Parks and Recreation, 1940 (Box 8B)
- Annual Report of the Division of Parks and Recreation, 1950-1951 (Box 8B)
- Fifth Annual Report, 1920 (Box 8B)
- Reports of the Immigration Commission Vol. 14-21, 1911 (Box 9)
- Reports of the Immigration Commission Vol. 22-24, 1911 (Box 9A)
- Bulletin of The Council for Social Service of the Church of England in Canada, 1917 June-1921 December; 2 folders (Box 10)
- Bulletin of The Council for Social Service of the Church of England in Canada, 1917 June-1921 December (Box 10)
- Proceedings of the Second Annual Meeting Held in Ottawa (Box 10)
- The Religious Outlook, 1919-1920 (Box 10)
- Bulletin of Oxford University Institute of Statistics, 1946 (Box 10)
- An Historical Study of Urban Missionary Work at Trinity Church in the City of New York, 1956 (Box 10)
- The Prediction of Personal Adjustment, 1941 (Box 10)
- Labor-management Relations: A Research Planning Memorandum by John G. Turnbull, 1949 (Box 10)
- Research on Labor Mobility: An Appraisal of Research Findings in the United States by Herbert S. Parnes, 1954 (Box 10)
- Theory and Practice in Historical Study: A Report of the Committee on Historiography, 1946 (Box 10)
- All Colors: A Study Outline on Woman's Part in Race Relations, 1926 (Box 10)
- Chicago's Negro Population: Characteristics and Trends, 1956 June (Box 10)
- Local Community Fact Book for Chicago, 1950, 1953 (Box 10)
- Red Wing and the Postwar Challenge by Roland S. Vaile, 1946 (Box 10)
- Public Health and Medical Care: In Red Wing and Goodhue County, 1946 (Box 10)
- Red Wing Looks Ahead: The Economic Impact of the War on a Minnesota Community, with a Forecast of Postwar Conditions, 1944 (Box 10)
- Medical Services in Jamaica by Mary Manning Carly, 1943 (Box 10)
- Economics in a Changing World by Graham A. Laing, 1936 (Box 10)
- The Modern Economy in Action by Caroline E. Ware, 1936 (Box 10)
- Government, Business, and the Individual by Elizabeth Stoffregen May, 1936 (Box 10)
- Louisville Surveys Its Needs: A Report to the Citizens of Louisville, Mississippi, 1954 (Box 10)
- A Study of Organized Communities in Mississippi, 1953 (Box 10)
- Religion and the Good Society (Box 10)
- International Survey of Legal Decisions on Labour Laws, 1929 (Box 11)
- Labor Laws of Maryland (15 Issues), 1933 (Box 11)
- Labor Laws of Maryland, 1933 (Box 11)
- State and Federal Mining Laws, 1947 (Box 11)
- State and Federal Mining Laws, 1949 (Box 11)
- Labor Laws of Maine/ Revision of 1955 (Box 11)
- Labor Laws of Maine/ Revision of 1959 (Box 11)
- Legislative Series 1956 (50 Issues), 2 folders (Box 11)
- Legislative Series: a general subject index (119 Issues), 1951; 2 folders (Box 11)
- Legislative Series: a general subject index (81 Issues), 1946; 2 folders (Box 11)
- 1951 Study of the Intermountain Area by David W. Barry and Ross W. Sanderson (Box 12)
- Foreign Service Bulletin, 1944-1947 (Box 12)
- Unitarian Medical Mission to Columbia, 1948 (Box 12)
- Information Service (253 copies), 1951-1956 (Box 12)
- Bulletin No. 1-159, 1917-1940 (Box 12)
- Investigations of Industries in New York City, 1921 (Box 12)
- Training for Library Service (3 copies), 1923 (Box 12)
- Forty Year Report of the New York Foundation 1909-1949, 1950 (Box 12)
- New York Foundation: Two Year Report 1954-1955 (Box 12)
- New York Foundation: Two Year Report 1956-1957, 1958 (Box 12)
- Toward the Paraproprietal Society, 1960 (Box 12)
- List of Books (With References to Periodicals) on Immigration, 1907 (Box 12)
- Bibliography on the Japanese in American Agriculture, 1944 (Box 12)
- Select List of References on Chinese Immigration, 1907 (Box 12)
- List of Discussions of the Fourteenth and Fifteenth Amendments with Special Reference to Negro Suffrage, 1906 (Box 12)
- Select List of References on the Negro Question, 1903 (Box 12)
- A Bibliography for Social Workers Among Foreign-born Residents of the United States, 1920 (Box 12)
- Select List of References on Capital Punishment, 1912 (Box 12)
- List of References on Prison Labor, 1915 (Box 12)
- Clothing Bulletin, 1943-1951 (Box 12)
- The British Benefactions of Andrew Carnegie, 1936 (Box 12)
- Carnegie Corporation of New York Quarterly, 1955-1964 (Box 12)
- Arts Teaching Equipment for Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 12)
- Progress & Problems in Education for Librarianship, 1946 (Box 12)
- Occupations for College Women, 1929 (Box 12)
- Selected Bibliography for Inter-racial Understanding, 1944 (Box 12)
- Bibliography on Censorship and Propaganda, 1921 (Box 12)
- Spirit Mound Township in the 1960 Election - A Study of Rural Attitudes Towards Issues, Candidates, and Campaign Appeals, 1961 (Box 12)
- South Dakota Political Almanac: a Presentation and Analysis of Election statistics, 1889-1960, 1962 (Box 12)
- Review of Grants to Colleges and Universities in the United States 1911-1932 No. 12, 1933 (Box 12)
- Review for Grants for Library Interests 1911-1935 No. 19 (Box 12A)
- The Corporation: A Digest of its Financial Record 1911-1936 No. 22 (Box 12A)
- The Development of Junior College Libraries No. 25, 1937 (Box 12A)
- The Corporation & The Jeanes Teacher No. 27, 1938 (Box 12A)
- Music Study Material: Preparation and Distribution of Sets No. 32, 1941 (Box 12A)
- The Art of Leadership by Ordway Tead, 1935 (Box 12A)
- Social Workers' Guide to the Serial Publications of Representative Social Agencies, 1921 (Box 12A)
- Free Synagogue Pulpit: Sermons and Addresses, 1908-1933 (Box 12A)
- The Church in Urban America, 1938 (Box 12A)
- Handbook for South Dakota County Officials, 1954 (Box 12A)
- 1961 Directory of State and Federal Officials in South Dakota (Box 12A)
- Problems in Intercultural Health Programs, 1958 (Box 12A)
- Effects of Social and Cultural Systems in Reaction to Stress, 1958 (Box 12A)
- International Wage Comparisons - A Report of Two International Conferences and a Critical Review of Available Statistical Data, 1932 (Box 12A)
- Heredity and Environment - A Critical Survey of Recently Published Material on Twins and Foster Children, 1941 (Box 12A)
- Report for 1944, 1945, and 1946, 1947 (Box 12A)
- Bibliographies on Personality and Social Development of the Child, 1953 (Box 12A)
- Social Status and Public Health, 1958 (Box 12A)
- Research in Social Psychology of Rural Life: Scope and Method, 1933 (Box 12A)
- Research Memorandum on Population Redistribution Within the United States, 1938 (Box 12A)
- Stabilization of Employment is Good Management, 1953 (Box 12A)
- University of Omaha Bulletin: Social Ministry in an American City, 1924 (Box 12A)
- The Ohio Sociologist - Bulletin of the Ohio Sociologist Society (11 Volumes), 1927-1930 (Box 12A)
- Conditions and Trends in Education for Librarianship, 1936 (Box 12A)
- Carnegie Grants for Library Buildings 1890-1917, 1943 (Box 12A)
- Statements of Carnegie Corporation of New York Submitter to Special Committee to Investigate Tax Exempt Foundations, 1954 (Box 12A)
- Selected Bibliography on the Negro, 1951 (Box 12A)
- Thirty Year Catalog of Grants (2 Copies), 1942 (Box 12A)
- Honduras: A Problem in Economic Development, 1959 (Box 12A)
- Family Mobility in Dallas, Texas, 1923-1938, 1942 (Box 12A)
- Population Mobility in Austin, Texas 1929-1931, 1941 (Box 12A)
- The Great Southwest Strike, 1942 (Box 12A)
- Handbook for South Dakota Municipal Officials, 1954 (Box 12A)
- Hospital and Medical Care for the Needy, 1955 (Box 12A)
- Handbook for South Dakota County Officials, 1961 (Box 12A)
- Papers of the Institute of Research and Training in the Social Sciences: Vanderbilt University, 1941-1944 (Box 12A)
- Survey of the Schools of West Hartford, 1922-1923 (Box 12A)
- Annual Report, 1921-1926 (Box 12B)
- Annual Report, 1935-1939 (Box 12B)
- Annual Report, 1927-1930 (Box 12B)
- Annual Report, 1931-1934 (Box 12B)
- Annual Report, 1940 (Box 12B)
- Annual Report, 1949 (Box 12B)
- Annual Report, 1947 (Box 12B)
- Annual Report, 1946 (Box 12B)
- Annual Report, 1944 (Box 12B)
- Annual Report, 1939 (Box 12B)
- First Annual Report of the Directors of the Massachusetts Infant Asylum, 1868-1899 (Box 12B)
- Bulletin of the American Friends Service Committee (Box 12B)
- The Cleveland Year Book/Chronological Index (2 copies 1926, 11 books), 1921-1930 (Box 13)
- International Survey of Legal Decisions on Labour Laws /Chronological Index, 1925-1928; 2 folders (Box 13)
- International Survey of Legal Decisions on Labour Laws /Chronological Index, 1930 (Box 13A)
- International Survey of Legal Decisions on Labour Laws /Chronological Index, 1931 (Box 13A)
- International Survey of Legal Decisions on Labour Laws /Chronological Index, 1932 (Box 13A)
- International Survey of Legal Decisions on Labour Laws /Chronological Index, 1933 (Box 13A)
- Annuaire de la Legislation Du Travail/Chronological Indexes (3 Issues), 1906-1908 (Box 13A)
- Report on the Physical Welfare of Mothers and Children, 1917 (Box 13A)
- Legislative Series Part I, II, III, 1931; 2 folders (Box 14)
- Legislative Series 1957 (77 Issues), 1959; 5 folders (Box 14)
- Legislative Series 1959 (87 Issues), 1961; 2 folders (Box 14)
- Bureau International du Travail Serie legislative (104 Issues), 1939-1964; 2 folders (Box 15)
- Legislative Report: A Current Summary on Labor Legislation (19 Issues), 1949 (Box 15)
- Legislative Series 1949 (147 Issues), 1952; 2 folders (Box 15)
- The Annual Report of the Cleveland Foundation, 1926-1974 (Box 15A)
- Survey of Post-war Social Development in the Netherlands, 1951 (Box 16)
- The Volunteer, 1957-1961 (Box 16)
- The Volunteer, 1962-1964; 2 folders (Box 16)
- The Volunteer, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
- Security for Canadians by Charlotte Whitton, 1943 (Box 16)
- The Unarmed forces by David Malcolm Young, 1943 (Box 16)
- William Penn's Plan for a League of Nations, 1919 (Box 16)
- Under the Red and Black Star: A Service of Spiritual Reconstruction (Box 16)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1941-1943 (Box 16A)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1944-1946 (Box 16A)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1947-1949 (Box 16A)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1950-1951 (Box 16A)
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation Annual Report, 1951-1952 (Box 16A)
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation Annual Report, 1952-1953 (Box 16A)
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation Annual Report, 1953-1954 (Box 16A)
- W.K. Kellogg Foundation Annual Report, 1961-1962 (Box 16A)
- Annuaire de la Legislation Du Travail/Chronological Indexes, 1899 (Box 17)
- Annuaire de la Legislation Du Travail/Chronological Indexes (4 Issues), 1902-1905 (Box 17)
- Annuaire de la Legislation Du Travail/Chronological Indexes (2 Issues), 1909-1910 (Box 17)
- International Survey of Legal Decisions on Labour Laws /Chronological Index (4 surveys), 1934-1938 (Box 17A)
- Legislative Series 1947 (116 Issues), 1949; 2 folders (Box 18)
- Legislative Series 1960, 1963; 2 folders (Box 18)
- Legislative Series 1961, 1963; 2 folders (Box 18)
- The Society of Friends of Roumania, The Society of Friends of Roumania Bulletin Dedicated to Her Majesty Queen Marie of Roumania, 1926 (Box 19)
- The Parliament of the Commonwealth of Australia, Secret Drugs, Cures, and Foods Report of the Royal Commission on (Volume 1), 1907 (Box 19)
- International Labour Office, Protection of Children and Young Workers. (a) Medical Examination for Fitness for Employment (Young Workers) (b) Restriction of Night Work of Children and Young Persons (Non-Industrial Occupations), 1945 (Box 19)
- International Labour Office, Reduction of Hours of Work., 1933 (Box 19)
- International Labour Office, Recruiting, Placing and Conditions of Labour (Equality of Treatment) of Migrant Workers, 1938 (Box 19)
- International Labour Office, Unemployment Insurance and Various Forms of Relief for the Unemployed., 1933 (Box 19)
- Housing Act, 1935. Report on the Overcrowding Survey in England and Wales, 1936 (Box 19)
- London, H. M. Stationary Office, Darling and Son, Limited, Second Interim Report on an investigation of industrial Fatigue by Physiological Methods, 1916 (Box 19)
- Ireland Local Government Board, Tuberculosis in Ireland, 1908 (Box 19)
- Great Britain, Ministry of Reconstruction, Advisory Housing Panel, Housing in England and Wales, Memorandum by the Advisory Housing Panel on the Emergency Problem, 1918 (Box 19)
- Great Britain, Committee to Collect Information on Russia, Information on Russia, Report (Political and Economic) of the Committee to Collect Information on Russia, 1921 (Box 19)
- Hundred New Towns Association, 100 New Towns for Britain: A Scheme of National Reconstruction, 1934 (Box 19)
- Carnegie United Kingdom Trust, Report of the Proceedings (of the ) County Library Conference, Held in the College of Preceptors Bloomsbury Square, London, W. C., 1924 November 4-6 (Box 19)
- Carnegie United Kingdom Trustees, A Report on Library Provisions and Policy, 1915 (Box 19)
- Carnegie United Kingdom Trust, The Public Library System of Great Britain and Ireland, 1921-1923, 1924 (Box 19)
- Carnegie United Kingdom Trust, A Report on American Museum Work, 1928 (Box 19)
- Carnegie United Kingdom Trust, A Report on the Public Museums of the British Isles (Other than the National Museums), 1928 (Box 19)
- Washington Government Printing Office, Mineral Resources of the United States, 1922, Part 1, Metals, 1925 (Box 19)
- New York Research Department, The Wage Question, 1922 (Box 19)
- Methods of Providing Rest and Alternation of Shifts in Automatic Sheet-Glass Works, 1933 (Box 19)
- Great Britain, Royal Commission of Tuberculosis, Interim Report of the Royal Commission Appointed to Enquire into the Relations of Human and Animal Tuberculosis, 1904 (Box 20)
- Great Britain, Royal Commission on Tuberculosis, Final Report of the Royal Commission Appointed in Inquire into the Relations of Human and Animal Tuberculosis, Volume 1-5 and Supplement, 1911 (Box 20)
- New Jersey State Chamber of Commerce, Department of Governmental Research, Teacher's Retirement Systems in New Jersey, Their Fallacies and Evolution, 1918 (Box 20)
- American Association of University Women St. Louis Branch, The Expenses of Women College Students: A Survey of 114 Colleges and Universities, 1922 (Box 20)
- Commonwealth Housing Commission Final Report, 1944 August 25 (Box 20)
- National Association of Hosiery Manufacturers (U.S.), Recent Changes in Hourly Earnings of Employees in the Hosiery Industry, 1929, 1933-1935 (Box 21)
- Cleveland Foundation, A Study of Public Relation in Cleveland, 1936 (Box 21)
- Palgrave's Dictionary of Political Economy, Vol. 3, N-Z, 1926 (Box 21)
- Wilson, Robert, The Science of Public Welfare, 1928 (Box 21)
- Educational Finance Inquiry Commission; American Council on Education, The Financing of Education in the State of New York, 1923 (Box 21)
- Educational Finance Inquiry Commission; American Council on Education, Bibliography on Education Finance, 1924 (Box 21)
- Huxley, Thomas Henry, Social Disease and Worse Remedies; Letter to the "Times" on Mr. Booth's Scheme, 1891 (Box 21)
- Salvation Army, What is the Salvation Army, 1945 (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, 1943 Volunteer Service Projects (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, International Service Seminars (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Peacetime Conscription: A Problem for Americans (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Under Red and Black Star, 1946 (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Under Red and Black Star, 1944 (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Under Red and Black Star, 1944 (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Under Red and Black Star, 1943 (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Building Tomorrow's World Today (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Quaker Relief in France (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Harvest (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Dispossessed (Box 21)
- American Friends Service Committee, Friends Civilian Public Service: Statement of Policy, 1943 (Box 21)